hibbett.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy

Date of Last Revision: May 29, 2018

**_Introduction_**

Welcome!  You have arrived at a web site that is provided by Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc., its affiliates or subsidiaries (collectively, “ **Hibbett** ,” **we** ,” “ **our** ,” or “ **us** ”).  This “ **Privacy Policy** ” governs your use of [www.hibbett.com](http://www.hibbett.com/) (including, without limitation, both mobile and online versions of our site) or any Hibbett Mobile App, and also applies to your use of all features, applications, social media channels, content, downloads and other services that we make available through the site and/or that post a link to this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to entry into a Hibbett Promotion, registering as a member of Hibbett Rewards, subscribing to Hibbett Mobile Alerts (Hibbett’s SMS text message program), subscribing to Hibbett Product Launch Alerts (another Hibbett SMS text message program) participating in one of our email or internet marketing campaigns, or in our stores through communications with Hibbett team members or with other Hibbett employees, or any other communication with Hibbett or any Hibbett employee (collectively, referred to herein as the “ **Platform** ”), regardless of how you access or use the Site, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise. 

The information you share with Hibbett allows us to provide the products and services you need and want while giving you the very best shopping experience.  By interacting with Hibbett through the Platform, you thereby consent and agree to the use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy and in the [Terms of Use](https://www.hibbett.com/customer-service/terms/terms-conditions.html). 

**To the extent we provide you notice on our Platform of different or additional privacy policies or practices (e.g., at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.**

**This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the[Terms of Use](https://www.hibbett.com/customer-service/terms/terms-conditions.html).  Each time that you access or use the Platform you signify that you agree to be bound by the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.  Please review the Terms of Use along with this Privacy Policy, _INCLUDING THE AGREEMENT TO ARBITRATE AND CLASS ACTION WAIVER PROVISIONS BELOW._**

**_Linkable Table of Contents_**

It is important that you read and understand the entire Privacy Policy before using the Site.  However, this table of contents highlights key issues and points and you can click on the headings and the “ _More_ ” links to be taken to the full explanation.

  1. **_What Information Do We Collect?_**

**_a. Information You Provide To Us_**

You may provide us with personal information and demographic information such as when you order a product, contact us, register an account, or sign up to receive information from us on the Platform.  **More**

**_b. Information We Collect and Store As You Access and Use the Platform_**

Certain information may be collected from you automatically through various technologies when you access and use the Platform.  **More**

**_c. Information Third Parties Provide About You_**

We may receive information about you from other sources.  **More**

**_d. Interactions With Third-Party Services_**

If you interact with third-party services, those services may send us information about you and you or we may send them information about you.  **More**

**_e. Information You Provide About a Third Party_**

You may provide us information about others, such as when you send a friend a message through our Platform.  **More**

**_f. California Do Not Track Disclosures_**

We currently do not offer an option to send “do not track” signals, but you may have certain other options regarding tracking and/or targeting.  **More**

  1. **_How Do We Use Your Personal Information?_**

We use your personal information for a variety of purposes detailed in this section.   **More**

  1. **_How and When Do We Share Your Personal Information?_**

We may provide your information to third parties under various circumstances detailed in this section.

  1. **_Your California Privacy Rights_**

California residents may request information about sharing of certain personal information with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes by contacting us using the methods described in this section.  **More**

  1. **_Ads and Information About You_**

We and third parties may send you targeted ads based on your browsing and shopping history.  If you object, you can exercise choices some third parties may offer.  **More**

  1. **_Does Your Platform Include Links To Third-Party Content, Sites, and/or Apps?_**

We may allow you to access third-party content on the Platform, or to link to third-party applications and locations from the Platform, but we are not responsible for your interaction with third-party content, apps, and locations.  **More**

  1. **_How Do I Change My Personal Preferences?_**

You may change certain information and preferences, and access information provided to us.  **More**

  1. **_Can My Data Be Transferred to the United States?_**

Data may be transferred to the United States.  **More**

  1. **_How Is My Personal Information Protected?_**

No data security is absolute, but we take reasonable steps to secure your data appropriately.  **More**

  1. **_What About Children’s Personal Information?_**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children without permission from a parent or guardian.  If you think we have, let us know.  **More**

  1. **_Can This Privacy Policy Be Updated?_**

We may change this Privacy Policy as detailed in this section.  **More**

  1. **_What Law Governs This Privacy Policy and How Will Disputes Be Resolved?_**

Legal disputes with respect to this Privacy Policy are detailed in this section.  **More**

  1. **_How May I Contact Hibbett?_**

You may contact us by email, phone, or mail, as detailed in this section.   **More**

### The Full Detailed Privacy Policy

  1. **What Information Do We Collect?**

**a.  Information You Provide To Us**

We collect information we receive from you, from your activities on the Platform, or through purchases you make from us.  Information we receive from you may include, but is not limited to, information you share with us when you order a product on Hibbett.com or a Hibbett Mobile App, enter a Hibbett Promotion, register as a member of Hibbett Rewards, subscribe to Hibbett Mobile Alerts, participate in one of our email or internet marketing campaigns, or communicate with our employees.

You share information with us in various ways in our stores and online.  For example, you may share information with us when you:

  * Purchase a product at Hibbett.com or on a Hibbett Mobile App
  * Download or use any portion of our website, Hibbett.com
  * Use a Hibbett Mobile App
  * Purchase a product in one of our stores
  * Register for a Hibbett account at Hibbett.com (which also registers you for Hibbett Rewards)
  * Register for Hibbett Rewards
  * Subscribe to Hibbett Mobile Alerts, Hibbett’s SMS text messaging service
  * Subscribe to Hibbett Product Launch Alerts,  another Hibbett SMS text messaging service
  * Request customer service or otherwise contact us
  * Post a review or comment on one of our social media pages
  * Participate in a contest, promotion, or survey
  * Submit User Created Content (as defined in the Terms of Use) (insert hyperlink) via the Platform or one of our online marketing or advertising campaigns
  * File a claim or complaint, request an investigation of any kind, or participate in same
  * Communicate with one of our team members at one of our stores regarding products, purchases, and other matters, including communications regarding use of Hibbett.com or a Hibbett Mobile App for any purpose, including ordering product
  * Otherwise communicate information to us
  *  

When you engage in these activities you may share different types of information with us, including:

  * First and Last Name
  * Date of Birth or Age
  * Gender
  * Mailing Address
  * Email Address
  * Telephone or Mobile Number
  * Credit or Debit Card Account Number
  * PayPal Account Information
  * Apple Pay Information
  * Social Media Information, including but not limited to Facebook, Instagram or Twitter ID

**b. Information We Collect and Store As You Access and Use the Platform**

We and third parties acting on our behalf for our business purposes also collect information that you provide to us through various technologies, such as through a cookie placed on your computer when you visit Hibbett.com.  This information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “Device”) whenever you visit or interact with our Platform.  This information may be non-identifying or may be associated with you.  Whenever we associate any non-identifying information with your personal information, we will treat it as personal information.

Further, third parties may use similar tracking technologies in connection with our Platform, which may include the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services.  We may not control those tracking technologies and we are not responsible for them.  However, you consent to potentially encountering third-party tracking technologies in connection with use of our Platform and accept that our statements under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the tracking technologies or practices of such third parties.

You also provide us with information in other ways through various technologies.  Some of this information may be linked to your device without your knowledge.  This information helps our website and/or Mobile App work correctly and supports our customer marketing and analytics efforts, thereby improving the experience we offer.  Here are some examples:

  * We or third parties acting on our behalf collect technical information when you visit our websites, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address, your device operating system and browser type, a unique device identifier, the path you take through our websites, and other information about your session on our websites.

  * We or third parties acting on our behalf may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through your computer or mobile device.  This information helps us recognize you, making our marketing efforts more relevant, and it includes, but is not limited to: the pages you visit on our website, which web address you came from, the type of browser/device/hardware you are using, purchase information and checkout process, search terms, and IP-based geographic location.  We use this information to market to you through third party advertising companies that display advertising information to you online based upon your browsing and shopping history.  These companies may employ cookies, web beacons and other technologies to measure advertising effectiveness.  You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish.  The help function of your browser should include instructions regarding your cookie settings, including how to set your device to not receive cookies.  If you set your device to not receive cookies you may not be able to access all features and functionality of our websites.  See AboutCookies.org for more information about the cookies.

  * We also operate in-store cameras for security and operational purposes, which help us to improve the design of our stores and to serve our customers.

  * We collect information directly from you to improve customer service.  For example, when you choose to send an email to any of our email addresses (@hibbett.com), you are, by default, also sending us your email address.  After we receive your email, we store your provided email address and content so that we may properly address your questions and concerns.

Hibbett does not store or save in its systems credit card, debit card, PayPal, or other financial account information. All payment processes are executed and managed by third parties on behalf of Hibbett. 

**c. Information Third Parties Provide About You**

We also receive information from other sources to help us supplement our records and improve the experience we offer.  We collect information needed to support our business.

**d. Interactions With Third-Party Services**

The Platform may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Platform and your account on a third-party web site, application or other service.  The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including personal information, to us.  For example, we may provide third-party sites’ interfaces or links on the Platform to facilitate your sending a communication from the Platform.  We may use third parties to facilitate emails, Tweets or Facebook postings.  These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or other activities and these third parties’ practices are not subject to our Privacy Policy.  Hibbett may not control or have access to your communications through these third parties.  Further, when you use third-party sites or services, you are using their services and not our services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices.  You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Platform.

**e. Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may send someone else a communication from the Platform, such as sending an invitation to a friend.  If so, the information you provide (names, email addresses, mobile number, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used by us for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise.  Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Platform, your email address, mobile number, name or user name and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s).

**f. California Do Not Track Disclosures**

Currently, we do not offer the option for website visitors to make a “Do Not Track” election and do not have the capability to respond to electronic “Do Not Track” signals.  We reserve the right to add such capability to our website at any time in the future and we will notify visitors of this change in capability through an update to this Privacy Policy.

  1. **How Do We Use Your Personal Information?**

Hibbett uses your personal information to provide you products and services.  We also use your personal information to support our business functions, such as marketing, store operations, operation of Hibbett.com, and asset protection.

Some examples include:

  * To communicate with you about your requests;
  * To process your offers to purchase product on Hibbett.com and in our stores;
  * To register and service your Hibbett Rewards account;
  * To register and service your Hibbett Mobile Alerts subscription;
  * To register and service your Hibbett Product Launch Alerts subscription;
  * To personalize our advertising and improve customer service;
  * To help us improve your experience in our stores and websites;
  * To respond to reviews, comments or other feedback you provide us;
  * To process purchases with gift cards and track gift card balances;
  * To protect the security and integrity of our services and business; and
  * For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

  1. **How and When Do We Share Your Personal Information?**

We may share the information we collect with third parties under various circumstances.  These may include:

  * Within the corporate family of Hibbett Sports, Inc., which includes subsidiaries and affiliates, in order to provide you with products and services;
  * With companies that provide support services to us, including but not limited to e-mail providers, mobile marketing services, analytics providers, web hosting providers, printers, banks and payment processors, data enhancement, management or processing services, fraud prevention providers, shipping services providers, product vendors, advertising vendors and gift card processors;
  * With third parties administering sweepstakes, contests, and promotions;
  * With third-party drop-shippers;
  * To third parties when you request information from or provide information to them;
  * To comply with any administrative and legal requirements;
  * On social media such as Facebook, Twitter or Instagram if you have commented or tagged a post on our social media site or in connection with a Hibbett promotion;
  * If there is a sale or transfer of some or all of our or our affiliates’ business assets, we may transfer information regarding Hibbett customers as needed, and we may also retain such information; and
  * At your request.

If you are an applicant for employment with us and applying for one of our job openings via our website, we will not collect any information via one of our websites.  Upon beginning the application process, you will be redirected to one of our third party service providers.  We have contracted with these providers to employ appropriate security measures and protect the confidentiality, availability and integrity of the information you provide.  As such, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of all websites operated by any of our employment-related third party service providers for more information on the applicable company’s privacy practices.  Please also see Section 6 below for further information on third party links.

If you are a California resident, please see Section 4 below, entitled “Your California Privacy Rights,” for further information on your rights with respect to third party sharing.

  1. **Your California Privacy Rights**

As discussed above, we collect various types of personal information about you while you are on our website.  Under California law, if you are a resident of California you may make a written request to us to request how we have shared your information with nonaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year.  You may contact us at [privacy@hibbett.com](mailto:privacy@hibbett.com) or via U.S. Certified Mail, Return Receipt Requested to Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc., Attention: Chief Privacy Officer, 2700 Milan Court, Birmingham, Alabama  35211, or call Hibbett Customer Service at (844) 362-4422.

In response to your written request, we will provide you with a notice describing the cost-free means to opt-out of our sharing your information with nonaffiliated third parties (i.e., those with whom we do not share the same brand name), if the third party will use it for their direct marketing purposes.

Additionally, if you are a California resident under 18 years old and you have an account on Hibbett.com, you can request that we remove content that you have posted to our website or other online services.  To request removal of content or information, please email [privacy@hibbett.com](mailto:privacy@hibbett.com), write to us via U.S. Certified Mail, Return Receipt Requested, to Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc., 2700 Milan Court, Birmingham, Alabama  35211, ATTN: Chief Privacy Officer, or call Hibbett Customer Service at (844) 362-4422.

  1. **Ads and Information About You**

Data about your activities online is being collected on our Platform for use in providing advertising tailored to your individual interests.  We may use third parties such as network advertisers and ad exchanges to serve advertisements across the Internet and may use third party analytics service providers to evaluate and provide us and/or third parties with information about the use of these ads on third party websites and viewing of ads and of our content.  Third parties may offer you a choice as to whether or not to have your information collected for that purpose.  This section of the Privacy Policy provides details and explains how to exercise that choice.

You may see certain ads on our Platform and/or on other third-party websites across the Internet because we participate in advertising networks administered by third parties.  These networks track your online activities over time and across third party websites by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of the tracking technologies described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, and they use this information to show you advertisements (including our ads) that are tailored to your individual interests.  The information they collect includes information about your visits to our Platform, such as the pages you have viewed.  These third-party tracking technologies may be set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times; and (c) understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements that have been delivered to you.  You acknowledge and agree that associated technology may access and use your device and may set or change settings on your device in connection with the associated operations.  Note that any images (or any other parts of content) served by third parties in association with third-party ads or other content may act as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities.

This collection and ad targeting may take place both on our Platform and on third-party websites that participate in the ad network, such as websites that feature advertisements delivered by the ad network.  This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.  We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as a DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our Platform.  To learn more about how to opt out of Google’s use of cookies, visit the Google’s Ads Settings, [**here**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) **.   **To learn more about how to opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies, visit the DoubleClick opt-out page, [**here**](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en) **.**

As explained elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, third-party tracking technologies are not controlled by us, even if they use our technology to help store or collect data.  Statements regarding our practices do not apply to the methods for collecting information used by these third-party advertisers and others or the use of the information that such third parties collect.  The relevant third party’s terms of service, privacy policy, permissions, notices and choices should be reviewed regarding their collection, storage and sharing practices.  We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third-party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties.  Further, while we may use a variety of companies to serve advertisements on the website, you may wish to visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>, which provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative (“ **NAI** ”) members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including the “opt-out” procedures of NAI members.  Opting out of one or more NAI members only means that those NAI members no longer will be allowed under their own rules to deliver targeted content and/or ads to you, which will affect this and other sites, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads.  Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different device or change web browsers, your NAI opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective.  Additional information is available on the NAI’s website accessible by the above link.  You may also be able to opt-out of receiving third-party behavioral ads by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (“ **DAA** ”) website at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/#completed).  Similar limitations may apply to the DAA opt-out.  We are not responsible for effectiveness of or compliance with any third-parties’ opt-out options.

  1. **Does Your Platform Include Links To Third-Party Content, Sites, and/or Apps?**

For your convenience, our Platform may contain content, links, or apps that are supplied by a third party and may direct you to a third party website.  The presence of any such content, links, or apps that appear on our website or other parts of our Platform should not be deemed to imply that we endorse or have an affiliation with the associated third party website.  We are not responsible for the data collection, privacy practices, or the content of such other websites.  We encourage you to review the separate privacy policies of each website that you visit.

  1. **How Do I Change My Personal Preferences?**

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration or a transaction.

You can generally access contact information and user preferences that you provide to us by logging into your account and accessing “My Account.”  To help protect your privacy and security, we will take steps we consider reasonable to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

You may cancel or modify our email marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional emails.  This will not affect subsequent subscriptions and if your opt-out is limited to certain types of emails the opt-out will be so limited.  Subsequent or different subscriptions will be unaffected.  Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of our Platform, such as administrative and Platform-related announcements and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing communications. 

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy or practices described in it, you should contact us by writing to Hibbett via U.S. Certified Mail, Return Receipt Requested, at 2700 Milan Court, Birmingham, Alabama  35211, ATTN: Chief Privacy Officer, or by calling us at (844) 362-4422.  We will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable (but we may retain prior information as business records).  Please note that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons.

  1. **Can My Data Be Transferred to the United States?**

Our Platform is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States.  If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including personal information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States.  The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States.  By using the Platform or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to the United States, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including personal information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Our Platform is not available to persons located in member countries of the European Union or the European Economic Area (“EEA”).Hibbett does not process personal data of data subjects in the European Union or the EEA related to the offer or sale of goods or services to data subjects in the European Union or the EEA.

Hibbett does not process personal data of data subjects in the European Union or the EEA related to the monitoring of behavior of persons in the European Union or the EEA as far as their behavior takes place within the European Union or the EEA.

  1. **How Is My Personal Information Protected?**

We take the security of the information you provide seriously.  We work to prevent unauthorized access and maintain data accuracy by employing security measures intended to deter unauthorized access to your information.  We use security measures, including physical, administrative and technical safeguards that we consider commercially reasonable and appropriate to protect the information you provide to us.  While we implement these security measures, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible and, as such, we disclaim all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, quiet enjoyment, and quality of information, title and non-infringement, and you waive all claims therefor.

  1. **What About Children’s Personal Information?**

Hibbett recognizes the importance of protecting privacy where children are involved.  As such, we do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 13 unless we first obtain permission from the child’s parent or legal guardian.  In the event we become aware that we have collected personal information from any child under the age of 13 without parental consent, we will dispose of that information in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) and other applicable laws and regulations.  If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent required by COPPA, we ask that you  email [privacy@hibbett.com](mailto:privacy@hibbett.com), write to us via U.S. Certified Mail, Return Receipt Requested, to Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc., at 2700 Milan Court, Birmingham, Alabama  35211, ATTN: Chief Privacy Officer, or call Hibbett Customer Service at (844) 362-4422.

  1. **Can This Privacy Policy Be Updated?**

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time.  Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy, and your use of our Platform indicates your consent to the Privacy Policy posted at the time of use.  However, we will not use your previously collected personal information in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent.  To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.

  1. **What Law Governs This Privacy Policy and How Will Disputes Be Resolved?**

Our website is published in the United States and is intended for users from the United States.  U.S. law, including the Federal Arbitration Act, shall govern in any and all disputes, including privacy or defamation issues or otherwise. You agree that the Federal Arbitration Act, applicable law, and the laws of the State of Alabama, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, and any dispute of any kind that might arise between you and Hibbett, including any privacy or defamation issues or otherwise. You agree to the following Agreement to Arbitrate and Class Action Waiver provision: 

**AGREEMENT TO ARBITRATE AND CLASS ACTION WAIVER**

YOU AND HIBBETT AGREE THAT: (1) ANY CLAIM, DISPUTE, OR CONTROVERSY MUST BE RESOLVED THROUGH ARBITRATION; (2) WE ARE EACH WAIVING THE RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY; (3) RIGHTS THAT WE EACH WOULD HAVE IF WE WENT TO COURT, SUCH AS DISCOVERY OR THE RIGHT TO APPEAL, MAY BE MORE LIMITED OR MAY NOT EXIST; (4) WE EACH MAY ONLY BRING A CLAIM IN OUR INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING; AND (5) THE ARBITRATOR MAY NOT CONSOLIDATE PROCEEDINGS OR CLAIMS OR OTHERWISE PRESIDE OVER ANY FORM OF A REPRESENTATIVE OR CLASS PROCEEDING.

Any claim that all or part of this class action waiver is unenforceable, unconscionable, void, or voidable may be determined only by a court of competent jurisdiction and not by an arbitrator.Any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to your use of the Platform, your Privacy, this Privacy Policy, User Created Content, your use of Content, or your purchase of a product using the Platform shall be settled by binding arbitration.You and Hibbett waive the right to go to court and agree to submit any claims to arbitration.This arbitration provision is governed by and enforceable under the Federal Arbitration Act (the “FAA”), 9 U.S.C. §§ 1-16, as amended.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we both retain the right to pursue in a small claims court any claim that is within that court’s jurisdiction and proceeds on an individual (non-class, non-representative) basis.With the exception of residents in New Jersey, you and Hibbett agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim must be filed within **one (1) year** after such claim arose or be forever barred.

The arbitration shall be administered by the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) in accordance with its Consumer Arbitration Rules issued in Sept. 2014.Please contact the AAA for a copy of the rules.For your convenience, the arbitration may be conducted in the federal district where you reside.It may be held by telephone or through written submissions if both you and Hibbett agree.Any award rendered shall include a written opinion and shall be final, subject to appeal under the FAA.This provision survives any termination of your access to the Platform or any other aspect of your relationship with Hibbett.If the class action waiver is deemed unenforceable, then this entire arbitration provision shall be rendered null and void.

YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TO OPT OUT OF THE ARBITRATION PROVISION WITHIN THIRTY DAYS OF YOUR FIRST USE OF THE PLATFORM OR YOUR PURCHASE OF A PRODUCT (WHICHEVER IS FIRST) BY WRITING TO US VIA U.S. CERTIFIED MAIL, RETURN RECEIPT REQUESTED, AT HIBBETT SPORTING GOODS, INC., 2700 MILAN COURT, BIRMINGHAM, AL35211, ATTN: LEGAL DEPT.

  1. **How May I Contact Hibbett?**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or the information you provided and we collected on our website, please feel free to contact us at [privacy@hibbett.com](mailto:privacy@hibbett.com), via U.S. Certified Mail, Return Receipt Requested, to Hibbett Sporting Goods, Inc., 2700 Milan Court, Birmingham, Alabama  35211, ATTN: Chief Privacy Officer, or call Hibbett Customer Service at (844) 362-4422.
